Finding Aid for the Ronald Bohn Collection of Film and Television Music Sound Recordings PASC-M.0105
UCLA Library Special Collections
Ronald Bohn collection of film and television music sound recordings
1955-1990
UCLA Library Special Collections
Bohn, Ronald L.
PASC-M.0105
74.5 Linear Feet (149 boxes)
The collection consists of commercially issued and other sound recordings, of music for television shows and motion pictures. The collection is in the midst of being processed. The finding aid will be updated periodically.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 997094183606533
Scope and Content
The collection consists of commercially-issued and other sound recordings, on 12 in. LP phonodiscs, of music for television shows and motion pictures.
The collection is arranged alphabetically by album title.
- 1976-1986: A Decade of Hits, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Scope and Contents note
  Ghostbusters -- Against All Odds (Take a Look at Me Now) -- Theme from Ice Castles (Through the Eyes of Love) -- The Greatest Love of All -- St. Elmo's Fire (Man in Motion) -- My Male Curiosity -- Freedom -- People Up in Texas -- It Might Be You (Theme from Tootsie) -- Electro-Phantasma -- Theme from Midnight Express -- (Closest Thing to) Perfect -- Savin' the Day -- Love Theme from St. Elmo's Fire -- Love Makes You Blind --Showdown -- Theme from Close Encounters of the Third Kind -- The Moment of Truth -- (It Takes Two)To Tango -- Separate Lives (Love theme from White Nights) -- Tap Dance -- Quicksilver Lightening -- One Day -- A Fine Mess -- Walk Through the Fire -- Prove Me Wrong -- One Love -- Cleanin' Up the Town -- Out of Bounds -- Fun Away -- Long as We Believe -- Working Girl March -- Love Theme from The Competition.
- 84 Charing Cross Road, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  General note
  Publisher no.: STV 81306
  Original motion picture soundtrack.
- 9 1/2 Weeks, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: SV-12470
- 9 to 5, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: T-627
- Die Abenteuer des Baron Munchhausen, 1988; 1 j12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: 925 826 1
- The Adventures of Baron Munchausen, 1988; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: 9 25826 1
- Against All Odds, 1984; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: 80152 1 E
  Music from the original motion picture soundtrack.
- Agatha, 1979; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: NBLP 7142
- Agnes of God, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: STV 81257
- Airplane, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: RY 9601
- The Alamo, 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: PC 8358
  Original sound track recording.
- Alcaiola, 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: TW 9102
- All That Jazz, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: NBLP 7198
- All That Jazz, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
- Altered States, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: ABL 13983
  Original soundtrack.
- Amadeus, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: WAM-1205
  Original soundtrack recording, volume 2.
- Amadeus, 1984; 2 12" sound discs (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: WAM 1791
  Original soundtrack recording.
- Amarcord Nino Rota, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: HNBL 9301
- American Pop, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: MCA 5201
- The Americanization of Emily, 1989; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: 6151
- The Americanization Of Emily, 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: SE-4271
- An Almost Perfect Affair, 1979; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: STV 81132
- An Unmarried Woman, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: T-557
- Annie Get Your Gun, 1963; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: 2360
  Also starring Robert Goulet.
- Annie, 1982; 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: JS 38000
- Armed and Dangerous, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: SJ 53041
  Music from the motion picture.
- Arthur 2: On the Rocks, 1988; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: SP 3916
- At the Drop of a Hat, 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: 35797
  Original cast album.
- Avalanche, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: DEL 25452
- The Awakening, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: ERS 6520
- Baby, 1984; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: 821593-1-Y-1
  Original Broadway cast recording.
- Babes in Toyland, 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: 56
- Band Wagon, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: MCA 25015
  Music from the original soundtrack.
- Bandolero, 1968; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: PR5026SD
- Barry Lyndon, 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: BS 2903
  Music from the soundtrack.
- Barry Lyndon, 1975; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
- Batman, 1989; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: 9 25977 1
  Original motion picture score.
- Batman, 1989; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: 9 25936 1
- The Beast, 1988; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: SP 3919
- The Bedroom Window, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: STV 81307
- Bernstein Conducts, 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: MS 6251
  West Side Story. Symphonic Dances -- On the Waterfront. Symphonic Suite.
- Beverly Hills Cop, 1984; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: MCA 5553
  Music from the motion picture soundtrack.
- The Big Chill, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: 6062MLA
- The Big Town, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: 7 81769 1
- Brighton Beach Memoirs, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: 6193
- Blame it on Rio, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: STV 81210
- Bless the Beats and Children, 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: SP 4322
  Original motion picture soundtrack recording.
- Blind Date, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: 70705
- Blue Thunder. Theme, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: MCA 13966
  Dance version.
- Blue Collar, 1973; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: MCA 3034
  Music from the original motion picture score.
- The Blue Lagoon, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: 2236X
- The Blue Max, 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: CT 6008
  The film score.
- Blue Velvet, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: STV 81292
- Blue Velvet, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
- The Blues Brothers, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: SD 16017
- Bob and Carol and Ted and Alice, 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: 1200
- Bobby Deerfield, 1977; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: NBLP 7071
- Boney, 1972; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: FL 34660
  Original TV soundtrack recording.
- Borsalino, 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: PAS 5019
  Original sound track of the film.
- The Boyfriend, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: MCA 39069
  The original motion picture soundtrack.
- Brainstorm, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: STV 81197
- The Breakfast Club, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: SP 5045
- Breakin', 1984; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: 821 919 1 Y 1
- A Bridge Too Far, 1977; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: UA LA762 H
- Brighton Beach Memoirs, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: MCA 6193
- Brigadoon, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: MCA 39062
- The Buddy Holly Story, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: 35412
- Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid, 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: SP 4227
  From the 20th Century Fox production.
- Bye Bye Birdie, 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: CP 454
- Cabaret, 1972; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: ABCD 752
- California Suite, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: JS 35727
- Camelot, 1973; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: S 32602
- Can-Can, 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: W1301
  Original soundtrack album.
- Candide, 1974; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: S2X 32923
  Original cast recording of the complete production.
- Carousel, 1965; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: LSO-1114
  On container, "Music theater of Lincoln Center."
- Casey's Shadow, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: 35344
- The Champ, 1979; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: P 9001
- Changing Faces, 1996; 1 12" Sound Disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: 92709
  New music from High School High the soundtrack.
- Che!, 1982; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: AEI 3111
- Children of a Lesser God, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: GNPS-8007
- A Chorus Line, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
- Christine, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: 6086 ML
- Cinderella Story, 1973; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: ST-100
- Clockwork Orange, 1972; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: BS 2573
- Close Encounters. Disco Version, 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Master recording.
- Close Encounters. The Five Tones, 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
- Cocoon, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: PDS 16418
- The Color Purple, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
- A Comedy Spectacular, 1979; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: AL 9510
- Comedy's Greatest Hits, 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: HF1801
- The Company of Wolves, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: STV 81242
- Cousteau Amazon, 1984; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: STV 81220
  The original television score.
- Count Basie: Dance Session, 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: MG C 626
- Crossroads, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: 9 25399 1
- Crossroads, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
- A Damsel in Distress -- The Sky's the Limit, 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: 100/19
  Two all-time-great soundtrack recordings.
- The Dark Crystal, 1982; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: 237491
  The original sound track.
- Das Boot, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: SD 19348
- Days of Heaven, 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: PAC8-128
  The original soundtrack from the motion picture.
- Dead Heat, 1988; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: 704.570
- The Destroyer, 1982; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: MCA 6135
  Music from the motion picture sound track.
- Diva, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: SL 9503
- Divorce American Style, 1967; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: UAS 5163
- D.O.A., 1988; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: 704.610
- Doctor Zhivago, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: MCA-39042
  The original sound track album.
- The Dove, 1974; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: ABDP-852
  The original soundtrack.
- Down and Out in Beverly Hills, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: MCA-6160
- Duck, You Sucker, 1972; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: UAS-5221
- Dueling Banjos, 1973; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: BS 2683
  From the original sound track of "Deliverance."
- The Eagle Has Landed, 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
- Earth Quake, 1974; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: MCA-2081
  Music from the original motion picture soundtrack
- Eddie and the Cruisers, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: BFZ 38929
- The Electric Horseman, 1979; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: AL 36327
- Expo '67, 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: LAB 650S
- Fanny, 1961; 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: W 1416
- Fiddler on the Roof, 1964; 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: LSO 1093
  The original Broadway cast recording.
- Film Classics, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: ARL1-4020
- Filmtracks II, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: Moment 107
  On container, "The best of British film music."
- Follies in Concert, 1985; 2 12" sound discs (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: HBC2-7128
  Performers include: Licia Albanese, Carol Burnett, Liz Callaway, Betty Comden, Barbara Cook, Adolph Green, Andre Gregory, George Hearn, Howard McGillin, Erie Mills, Liliane Montevecchi, Phyllis Newman, Mandy Patinkin, Daisy Prince, Lee Remick, Arthur Rubin, Elaine Stritch, Jim Walton, and the New York Philharmonic.
- Funny Girl, 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: BOS 3220
- Funny Landy, 1975; 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: AL 9004
- Ghostbusters, 1984; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: AL8-8246
  Original soundtrack album
- Godspell. Selections, 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: GAR 11312
- The Golden Voyage of Sinbad, 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: UAS 29576
  Original motion picture sound track.
- Gone With the Wind, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: MCA 39063
  Original sound track album.
- Gone With the Wind, 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: SW 1322
- Gone With the Wind, 1974; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: ARL1 0452
  On container, "newly recorded."
- Good Morning Vietnam, 1988; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: SP 3913
- Goodbye, Mr. Chips, 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: S1E 19 STX
- Gorky Park, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: STV 81206
- Grease, 1978; 2 12" sound discs (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: RS 2 4002
- The Great Outdoors, 1988; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: 7 81859 1
- Great Balls of Fire, 1989; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: 839 516 1
- Guys and Dolls, 1976; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: M6 876S1
- Hair: the American Tribal Love Rock Musical, 1968; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: LSO 1150
- Halloween, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: STV 81176
- The Hallelujah Trail, 1982; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: AUSLP 1017
- Hang 'em High, 1968; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: LSP 4022
- Harry and the Hendersons, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: MCA 6208
- Harry and Tonto, 1974; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: NBLP 7010
- Harry and Tonto, 1974; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
- Harold Lloyd's World of Laughter, 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: CT 6018
  The Freshman -- World of Comedy.
  Original soundtrack recordings.
- The Harrad Experiment, 1973; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: ST 11182
- Hellbound: Hellraiser II, 1988; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: GNPS 8015
- High Spirits, 1988; 1 12" sound track (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: GNPS 8016
- Honk: Five Summer Stories, 1972; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: GF 7720
  Original sound track.
- Hope and Glory, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: STV 81329
- Housekeeping, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: STV 81338
- How Sweet It Is, 1968; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: SF 7988
  From the original sound track.
- How the West Was Won, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: MCA 39043
- How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying, 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: LOC 1066
  Original Broadway cast recording. Also composed by Abe Burrows.
- Humanoids From the Deep, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: CST 0203
- The Hunger, 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: STV 81184
  Original motion picture soundtrack. Also composed by Denny Jaeger.
- I Got Somebody Else, 1996; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: 0 95656
  New music from the High School High soundtrack.
- I Left My Heart in San Francisco, 1962; 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: CL 1869
- Ice Castles, 1979; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: AL 9502
- Inseminoid, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: CT 7023
- Invitation au Voyage, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: STV 81189
- Irma La Douce, 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: OS 2029
- It's Always Fair Weather, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Music from the Original soundtrack.
- It's My Turn, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: M8 947M1
- Jagged Edge, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: STV 81252
  Original motion picture soundtrack. Two copies.
- Jake Speed, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: STV 81285
- James Bond 007: 13 Original Themes, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: LJ 51138
- Jaws, 1975; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: MCA 2087
- Jaws 3-D, 1982; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: MCA 6124
- Jaws Two, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: MCA 3045
- Jo Jo Dancer Your Life is Calling, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: 254441
- Just One Of The Guys, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: 60426-1-E
  Original motion picture soundtrack
- The Karate Kid, 1984; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: 822213-1 M-1
- The Karate Kid II, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: SW 40414
- The Karate Kid Part III, 1989; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: MCA 6308
  Original motion picture soundtrack album.
- The Kentuckian, 1977; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: ERS 6506
  Great americana film scores.
- The King and I, 1956; 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: W740
  Motion picture soundtrack.
- Kings Row, 1979; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: SDG 305
  First recording of original score
- Kismet, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: MCA 1424
  Music from the original soundtrack
- Kiss Me Kate, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: MCA-25003
- Kostelanetz, 1976; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: KC 34157
- Krull, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: FILM 005
- La Bamba, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: 25605-1
- La Bamba, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
- Ladyhawke, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: 81248-1-E
- The Last Emperor, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: 90690-1
- The Last Emperor, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
- Latin ala Lee: Broadway Hits Styled With an Afro-Cuban Beat, 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: T1290
- Laurel And Hardy's Music Box, vol. 1, 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: MON LP024
- Legend, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: 100
- Legend, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: MCA-6165
  Music from the motion picture soundtrack
- Lena Horne: the Lady and Her Music, 1981; 2 12" sound discs (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: 2QW 3597
  On container, "Live on Broadway."
- Lena in Hollywood, 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: UAS 6470
- Lethal Weapon 2, 1989; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: 25985-1
  Original Motion Picture Soundtrack
- Little Dorrit, 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: 117
- Little Shop of Horros, 1982; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: GHSP 2020
- A Little Night Music, 1973; 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: KS 32265
- Local Hero, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: 23827-1
- Lolita, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: MCA 39067
- Lord Jim, 1965; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: 521
- The Lord of the Rings, 1978; 2 12" sound disks (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: LOR-1
- The Lords of Flatbush, 1974; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: ABCD-828
  The original sound track recording.
- Loss of Innocence, 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: CP 508
  Original movie soundtrack.
- Lost Horizon, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: GL 43445
- Love and Menace, 1989; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: RC 270
- Mad Max, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: STV 81144
- The Mad Adventures of "Rabbi" Jacob, 1973; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: PS 652
  The original soundtrack from the film by Gerard Oury.
- Major Dundee, 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: OL 6380
- Man of La Mancha, 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: KRS 5505
  Original cast recording.
- Marilyn Monroe, 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: 1000/1
- Midnight Express, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
- The Missouri Breaks, 1976; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: MCA-25113
- The Moon in the Guitar, 1982; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: SL 9516
- Moscow on the Hudson, 1984; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: ABL1-5036
- The Most Happy Fella, 1973; 3 12" sound discs (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: CO3L240
  The complete Broadway performance as presented on stage.
- Motown Presents Prime Time, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: M7-905R1
- My Fair Lady, 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: JS 2600
- National Lampoon's Animal House, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: MCA 1692
- The New Adventures of Pippi Longstocking, 1988; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: 91016-1
  Original soundtrack from the motion picture.
- The New Adventures of Pippi Longstocking, 1988; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: 28 MM 0627
- The Night of the Iguana, 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: PR 4
  Limited collector's edition. Dramatic highlights from the acclaimed film with commentary by John Huston.
- 1941, 1979; 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
- A Nous Deux, 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: 56664
  Bande originale du film de Claude Lelouch.
- Now Tom and Irma..Are Side By Side!, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: MCA-39068
- The Odessa File, 1974; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: MCA-2084
  Original soundtrack music.
- Oh God, II, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
- Oklahoma!, 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: SWAO 595
  From the sound track of the motion picture.
- Oliver!, 1963; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: LOCD-2004
- Oliver!, 1963; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: LSOD-2004
- Oliver, 1968; 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: COSD 5501
- On Golden Pond, 1982; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: MCA 6106
  Music and original dialog from the motion picture soundtrack.
- Once Upon a Time in the West, 1972; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: LSP-4736
  The original soundtrack recording.
- One Flew Over the Cuckoos Nest, 1975; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: F-9500
- Our Man in Hollywood, 1963; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: LPM-2604
- Paris, Texas, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: 25270-1E
- Patrick, 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: VC 81107
- Peggy Sue Got Married, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: STV 81295
- Penitentiary III, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: 6663-1-R
  Original soundtrack from the cannon motion picture.
- Perfect, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: AL9-8278
- Petulia, 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: 1755
- Picnic, 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: MCA 1527
  Music from the sound track.
- Pinocchio, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: 1202
- Playing for Keeps, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: 81678-1-E
- Platoon Leader, 1988; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: GNPS 8013
- Poltergeist, 1982; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: MG-1-5408
- Pretty Baby, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: AA 1076
  Music from the soundtrack of the Paramount motion picture.
- Prince of the City, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Publisher no.: STV 81137
- Promised Land, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 144)
  Original soundtrack from the Vestron motion picture.
- The Pursuit of D.B. Cooper, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: PD-1-6344